A Guide to Production Books for Arena Stage, 1950-2000
George Mason University Libraries
Special Collections and Archives, George Mason University
A Guide to Arena Stage Production Books 1950-2000
Special Collections and Archives, George Mason University
Arena 002
124 containers comprising 37 cubic feet (55 linear feet)
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Donated to George Mason University Libraries in the fall of 2000
Biographical Information
Arena Stage was an early leader in the resident theater movement. One of the first not-for-profit theaters in the United States as well as a pioneer of the regional theater movement the Arena Stage was the first regional theater to transfer a production to Broadway, the first invited by the U.S. State Department to tour behind the Iron Curtain and the first to receive a Tony Award. Co-founded in 1950 by Edward Mangum a teacher from the George Washington University, and Zelda Fichandler one of his students, Arena Stage was opened in Washington D.C. to fill the void left by the closing of the National Theater in 1948. Deriving it's name from the idea of "theater in the round," Arena Stage became one of the first resident theaters in the United States, beginning with a company of only eight actors. Today, Arena performs to over 250,000 patrons during a September to June season and employs nearly 200 theater professionals and craft persons, who are responsible for all the costumes and scenery seen on stage. Many now- famous actors took part in Arena Stage productions during the early part of their careers. Some of them include Robert Prosky, Morgan Freeman, Dianne Weist, James Earl Jones, Kevin Kline, Christopher Guest, Yeardly Smith and Samuel L. Jackson. Donated to George Mason University in fall of 2000, the Arena Stage Collection contains materials spanning the theater's 50 year history including production notebooks, photographs, playbills, scrapbooks, scripts and handwritten correspondence and other production materials.
Scope and Content
Contains production books, scripts (calling, acting, and blocking); props and set design information, and other miscellaneous production materials.
Arrangement
Alphabetical by production title
Contents List
- Arena Stage Production Books and Information
  - African Company - "Blood Knot" and "Richard III" production book, 1 of 2 (Box Box 1)
  - African Company - "Blood Knot" and "Richard III" production book, 2 of 2 (Box Box 1)
  - "Blood Knot" blocking notes (Box Box 1)
  - "Blood Knot" blocking notes (Box Box 1)
  - "All My Sons" rehearsal and performance notes (1999-2000) (Box Box 2)
  - "All My Sons" daily managers report, 2 programs (Box Box 2)
  - "All My Sons" rehearsal sch. and misc. paperwork (Box Box 2)
  - "All My Sons" calling script (Box Box 2)
  - "All My Sons" blocking script (Box Box 2)
  - "Almost Blue" prompt script (Box Box 3)
  - "The American Play" production book (Box Box 3)
  - "The American play" production book (Box Box 3)
  - :Antigone in New York" production materials (Box Box 3)
  - "Antigone in New York" production script (Box Box 3)
  - "Antigone in New York" production script (Box Box 3)
  - "Animal Cracker" contact info/program (Box Box 4)
  - "Animal Crackers" Sch. (Box Box 4)
  - "Animal Crackers" reh. notes (Box Box 4)
  - "Animal Crackers" run sheets (Box Box 4)
  - "Animals Crackers" props (Box Box 4)
  - "Animal Crackers", set/lx/sound (Box Box 4)
  - "Animal Crackers", memos (Box Box 4)
  - "Animal Crackers" performance reports (Box Box 4)
  - "Animal Cracker" accident reports (Box Box 4)
  - "Animal Crackers" reviews (Box Box 4)
  - "Animal Crackers", blocking script (Box Box 4)
  - "Animal Crackers" choreography book, 1 of 2 (Box Box 4)
  - "Animal Cracker" choreography book, 2 of 2 (Box Box 4)
  - "Animal Crackers" musical numbers, 1 of 2 (Box Box 5)
  - "Animal Crackers" musical numbers 2 of 2 (Box Box 5)
  - "Animal Crackers" score (Box Box 6)
  - "Animal Crackers" Mactha Knight's production book (Box Box 6)
  - "Animal Crackers" script (revised) (Box Box 6)
  - "Animal Crackers" script (revised) (Box Box 6)
  - "Animal Crackers" script (revised) (Box Box 6)
  - "Animal Crackers" call book (Box Box 6)
  - "Animal Crackers" script with production notes (Box Box 7)
  - "Animal Crackers" choreography (Box Box 7)
  - "Animal Crackers" misc. production materials (Box Box 7)
  - "Animal Crackers" script w/ production notes (Box Box 7)
  - "Animal Crackers" 2 scripts (Box Box 7)
  - "Arcadia", script with production notes (Box Box 8)
  - "Arcadia", script with production notes (Box Box 8)
  - "Arcadia", blocking script, tech. notes, actor research (Box Box 8)
  - "Arcadia" blocking script, tech. notes, actor research (Box Box 8)
  - "Arcadia" Blocking script, tech. notes, actor research (Box Box 8)
  - "Arcadia" sch., notes, memos (Box Box 8)
  - "Babes in Boyland", misc. production materials (Box Box 9)
  - "Babes in Boyland"script and misc. production notes (Box Box 9)
  - "Babes in Boyland", production book (Box Box 9)
  - "Babes in Boyland", production book (Box Box 9)
  - "Almost Blue", production notes (Box Box 10)
  - "Banjo Dancing", performance and safety reports (Box Box 10)
  - "Banjo Dancing", performance and safety reports (Box Box 10)
  - "Banjo Dancing", safety and performance reports (Box Box 10)
  - "Banjo Dancing", performance and safety reports (Box Box 10)
  - "Banjo Dancing" performance and safety reports (Box Box 10)
  - "Before it hits Home", blocking notes (Box Box 11)
  - "Before it hits Home" script with notes (Box Box 11)
  - "Before it hits Home", misc. production notes (Box Box 11)
  - "Blithe Spirit", SM/blocking book (Box Box 12)
  - "Blithe Spirit", SM/Blocking book (Box Box 12)
  - "Blithe Spirit", misc. production materials/notes (Box Box 12)
  - "Blithe Spirits", misc. production materials/notes (Box Box 12)
  - "Blithe Spirit", schedules and notes (Box Box 12)
  - "Blithe Spirit", schedules and notes (Box Box 12)
  - "Blood Knot", blocking book (Box Box 13)
  - "Blood Knot" calling book (Box Box 13)
  - "Blood Knot", calling books (Box Box 13)
  - "Blue", contact sheet / programs (Box Box 14)
  - "Blue" performance report (Box Box 14)
  - "Blue", accident report (Box Box 14)
  - "Blue", run sheets (Box Box 14)
  - "Blue", prompt book (Box Box 14)
  - "Blue", props (Box Box 14)
  - "Blue" costumes (Box Box 14)
  - "Blue", Daily notes (Box Box 14)
  - "Blue" schedules (Box Box 14)
  - "Blue", set/lights/sound (Box Box 14)
  - "Blue", script (Box Box 14)
  - "Blue", P.P. / education/access (Box Box 14)
  - "Blue", actor's packet:supplemental research for Blue (Box Box 14)
  - "Blues for an Alabama Sky", production book (Box Box 15)
  - "Born Guilty:, script (Box Box 16)
  - "Born Guilty", blocking book (Box Box 16)
  - "Born guilty", misc. production notes (Box Box 16)
  - "Born Guilty", prompt book (Box Box 17)
  - "Born Guilty", prompt book (Box Box 17)
  - "Born Guilty", misc. production notes (Box Box 17)
  - "Born Guilty", misc. production notes (Box Box 17)
  - "The Brothers Karamazov", blocking script (Box Box 18)
  - "Brothers Karamazov", blocking script (Box Box 18)
  - "Brothers Karamazov", blocking script (Box Box 18)
  - "The Brothers Karamazov", blocking script (Box Box 18)
  - "The Brothers Karamazov", blocking script (Box Box 18)
  - "Brothers Karamazov", blocking script (Box Box 18)
  - "The Brothers Karamazov", video, cassette tapes and large floppy discs of production materials (Box Box 19)
  - "Brothers Karamazov", production book (Box Box 19)
  - "Brothers Karamazov", misc. production notes (Box Box 19)
  - "Brothers Karamazov", script (Box Box 19)
  - "Candide", musical score (Box Box 20)
  - "Candide", Musical score (Box Box 20)
  - "Candide:, musical score (Box Box 20)
  - "Candide", script w/musical score (Box Box 20)
  - "Candide", script w/ musical score (Box Box 20)
  - "Candide". script w/ musical score (Box Box 20)
  - Candide: cast info, show reports, rehearsal sch. (Box Box 21)
  - Candide: blocking script (Box Box 21)
  - Candide: blocking script (Box Box 21)
  - Candide: blocking script (Box Box 21)
  - Candide: tech. notes (Box Box 21)
  - Candide: tech. notes (Box Box 21)
  - Candid: lighting and sound information (Box Box 22)
  - Candide: light and sound script (Box Box 22)
  - Candide: lighting and sound script (Box Box 22)
  - Caucasian Chalk Circle: production book (Box Box 23)
  - Caucasian Chalk Circle: script and misc. production notes (Box Box 23)
  - Caucasian Chalk Circle: blocking script (Box Box 23)
  - Caucasian Chalk Circle: blocking script (Box Box 23)
  - Caucasian Chalk Circle: costume sketches and tape of 1st rehearsal (Box Box 23)
  - Caucasian Chalk Circle: script, stage blue prints, and 1st rehearsal welcome speech by Zelda Fichandler (Box Box 23)
  - Caucasian Chalk Circle: musical score (Box Box 23)
  - Cat on a Hot Tin Roof: production book (Box Box 24)
  - Cat on a Hot Tin Roof: 2 programs and the daily stage managers report/rehearsal sch. (Box Box 24)
  - Cat on a Hot Tin Roof: accident report, production notes and actor's "packet" (Box Box 24)
  - Cat on a Hot Tin Roof: SM book (Box Box 24)
  - Cerceau: production book, 1 of 2 (Box Box 25)
  - Cerceau: Production book, 2 of 2 (Box Box 25)
  - Coming of the Hurricane: misc. production notes (Box Box 26)
  - Coming of the Hurricane: blocking and prompt script (Box Box 27)
  - Coming of the Hurricane: blocking and prompt script (Box Box 27)
  - Coming of the Hurricane: blocking and prompt script (Box Box 27)
  - A Community Carol: misc. production notes (Box Box 28)
  - A Community Carol: production book (Box Box 28)
  - A Community Carol: production book (Box Box 28)
  - A Community Carol: misc. production notes (Box Box 28)
  - A Community Carol: tech. info and call book (Box Box 28)
  - A Community Carol: blocking script (Box Box 28)
  - A Community Carol: blocking script (Box Box 28)
  - A Community Carol: misc production notes (Box Box 29)
  - A Community Carol: production book (Box Box 29)
  - A Community Carol: Production book (Box Box 29)
  - Dancing at Lughnasa: prompt book (Box Box 30)
  - Dancing at Lughnasa: misc. production material (Box Box 30)
  - Dance of Death: blocking script (Box Box 30)
  - Dance of Death: misc. production materials (Box Box 30)
  - Dimly Perceived Threats: blocking script (Box Box 31)
  - Dimly Perceived Threats: actors packet, blocking notes and misc. materials (Box Box 31)
  - Dimly Perceived Threats: stage blue prints (Box Box 31)
  - Dinah Was: performance reports (Box Box 32)
  - Dinah Was: music (Box Box 32)
  - Dinah Was: orchestrations (Box Box 32)
  - Dinah Was: review pack (Box Box 32)
  - Dinah Was: script (Box Box 32)
  - Dinah Was: calling script - extra (Box Box 32)
  - Dirty Work: production book (Box Box 33)
  - Dirty Work: script revisions and blocking notes (Box Box 33)
  - Dirty Work: final blocking script (Box Box 33)
  - Doll House: script and production notes (Box Box 34)
  - Doll House: Script with notes (Box Box 33)
  - East Texas Hot Links: production script with notes (Box Box 35)
  - East Texas Hot Links: script, performance reports, photos (Box Box 35)
  - East Texas Hot links: script and performance report (Box Box 35)
  - Eleanor: Her Secret Journey. script and program (Box Box 36)
  - Eleanor: Her Secret Journey. performance reports (Box Box 36)
  - Expecting Isabel: original and ugly calling script (Box Box 37)
  - Expecting Isabel: tech info (Box Box 37)
  - Expecting Isabel: Schedule/cast info (Box Box 37)
  - Expecting Isabel: blocking script (Box Box 37)
  - Expecting Isabel: music (Box Box 37)
  - Expecting Isabel: calling script (Box Box 38)
  - Expecting Isabel: corrected script (Box Box 38)
  - The Faraway Nearby: actors packet (Box Box 39)
  - The Faraway Nearby: cue list/ TOS preset/ performance report (Box Box 39)
  - The Faraway Nearby: run list/ rehearsal notes/ scene chart (Box Box 39)
  - The Faraway Nearby: tech week sch./ prop notes (Box Box 39)
  - The Faraway Nearby: review packet (Box Box 39)
  - The Faraway Nearby: script (Box Box 39)
  - Fences: prompt book/ show reports/ tech notes (Box Box 40)
  - Fences: script with blocking notes (Box Box 40)
  - First lady: script (Box Box 41)
  - First Lady: benefit information (Box Box 41)
  - First Lady: benefit info (Box Box 41)
  - For the Pleasure of Seeing Her Again: stage/house managers report (Box Box 42)
  - The Front Page: misc. production information (Box Box 43)
  - The Front Page: program and final script (Box Box 43)
  - Ghost: SM book and misc. production information (Box Box 44)
  - Glass Menagerie: blocking script (Box Box 45)
  - The Glass Menagerie: stage blue prints (Box Box 45)
  - Guys and Dolls: prompt book (Box Box 46)
  - Guys and Dolls: set/props/lights (Box Box 46)
  - Guys and Dolls: costume (photos and info sheets) (Box Box 46)
  - Guys and Dolls: daily notes (Box Box 46)
  - Guys and Dolls: schedules (Box Box 46)
  - Guys and Dolls: run sheets (Box Box 46)
  - Guys and Dolls: research 1 of 3 (Box Box 47)
  - Guys and Dolls: research 2 of 3 (Box Box 47)
  - Guys and Dolls: research 3 of 3 (Box Box 47)
  - Guys and Dolls: contact sheets / calendars (Box Box 47)
  - Guys and Dolls: accident reports (Box Box 47)
  - Guys and Dolls: out lists (Box Box 47)
  - Guys and Dolls: P/R and education (Box Box 47)
  - Guys and Dolls: back-up piano/conductor music sheets (Box Box 47)
  - Guys and Dolls: back-up piano/conductor music sheets (Box Box 47)
  - Hedda Gabler: sch., performance reports, and misc. production materials (Box Box 48)
  - Hedda Gabler: master script (Box Box 48)
  - Hedda Gabler: prompt script (Box Box 48)
  - Holiday Heart: script/props/ blocking notes/ music sheets (Box Box 49)
  - Holiday Heart: background information (Box Box 49)
  - Holiday Heart: blocking and prompt script (Box Box 49)
  - Holiday Heart: blocking and prompt script (Box Box 49)
  - Holiday Heart: blocking and prompt script (Box Box 49)
  - Hot 'N' Throbbing: program/contact sheet/ calendars (Box Box 50)
  - Hot 'N' Throbbing: run sheets (Box Box 50)
  - Hot 'N' Throbbing: props (Box Box 50)
  - Hot 'N' Throbbing: prompt book (Box Box 50)
  - Hot 'N' Throbbing: costumes (Box Box 50)
  - Hot 'N' Throbbing: set and lights (photographs) (Box Box 50)
  - Hot 'N' Throbbing: sound and video (Box Box 50)
  - Hot 'N' Throbbing: schedules (Box Box 50)
  - Hot 'N' Throbbing: research and background (Box Box 50)
  - House Arrest: production book (Box Box 51)
  - How I Learned to Drive: calling script (Box Box 52)
  - How I learned to Drive: blocking script (Box Box 52)
  - How I learned to Drive: review packet (Box Box 52)
  - How I learned to Drive: Reh. calendars (Box Box 52)
  - How I learned to Drive: cast list (Box Box 52)
  - How I learned to Drive: background info (Box Box 52)
  - How I Learned to Drive: performance report (Box Box 52)
  - How I Learned to Drive: rehearsal notes (Box Box 52)
  - How I Learned to Drive: script changes (Box Box 53)
  - How I Learned to Drive: on stage preset (Box Box 53)
  - How I Learned to Drive: slider cue sheet (Box Box 53)
  - How I Learned to Drive: props (Box Box 53)
  - How I Learned to Drive: props list (Box Box 53)
  - How I Learned to Drive: "Performing Arts" publication, January 1998 (Box Box 53)
  - How I Learned to Drive: Berkeley script (Box Box 53)
  - Hot 'N' Throbbing: performance report (Box Box 53)
  - Hot 'N' Throbbing: daily notes (Box Box 53)
  - Hot 'n' Throbbing: script changes (Box Box 53)
  - I am a Man: blocking script, Act I (Box Box 54)
  - I am a Man: blocking script, Act II (Box Box 54)
  - I am a Man: prompt book (Box Box 54)
  - I am a Man: prompt book (Box Box 54)
  - I ma a Man: prompt book (Box Box 54)
  - I'd Rather be Right: script (Box Box 55)
  - It Ain't Nothin' but the Blues: revised script and lighting book (Box Box 56)
  - It Ain't Nothin' but the Blues: script and preset list (Box Box 56)
  - It Ain't Nothing but the Blues: misc. production information (Box Box 56)
  - It Ain't Nothin' but the Blues: blocking script (Box Box 57)
  - It Ain't Nothing but the Blues: script (Box Box 57)
  - It's the Truth: Calling script and misc. notes (Box Box 57)
  - Jar the Floor: prompt book (Box Box 58)
  - Jar the Floor: prompt book (Box Box 58)
  - Jar The Floor: prompt book (Box Box 58)
  - Let Them Eat Cake: script (Box Box 59)
  - Life Go Boom: prompt book (Box Box 60)
  - Life Go Boom: prompt book (Box Box 60)
  - Life Go Boom: prompt notes (Box Box 60)
  - A Long Days Journey into Night: script and contact sheet (Box Box 61)
  - Long Days Journey into Night (Box Box 61)
  - Long Days Journey into Night: script (Box Box 61)
  - Long Days Journey into Night: blocking book (Box Box 61)
  - Long Days Journey into Night: blocking book (Box Box 61)
  - Long Days Journey into Night: SM's book (Box Box 61)
  - Lovers and Executioners: script and stage plans (Box Box 62)
  - Lovers and Executioners: misc. production materials (Box Box 62)
  - Lovers and Executioners: misc. materials (Box Box 62)
  - Lovers and Executioners: prompt book (Box Box 62)
  - Macbeth: script (Box Box 63)
  - Macbeth: tech. materials (Box Box 63)
  - MacBeth: misc. materials (Box Box 63)
  - The mad Dancers: script (Box Box 64)
  - The Matchmaker: production book (Box Box 65)
  - Match Maker: production notes and lists (Box Box 65)
  - Match maker: notes and lists (Box Box 65)
  - The Miracle Worker: script (Box Box 66)
  - The Miracle Worker: cast info, memos and tech. notes (Box Box 66)
  - The Miracle Worker: schedules and show reports (Box Box 66)
  - The Miracle Worker: items taken from the call board (Box Box 66)
  - The Miracle Worker (Box Box 66)
  - The Miracle Worker: blocking script (Box Box 66)
  - The Miracle Worker: calling script (Box Box 66)
  - Misalliance: prompt book, blocking script (Box Box 67)
  - The Miser: misc. production materials (Box Box 68)
  - The Miser: misc materials (Box Box 68)
  - The Miser: misc. (Box Box 68)
  - The Miser: prompt book (Box Box 68)
  - The Miser: prompt book (Box Box 68)
  - The miser: prompt book (Box Box 68)
  - Molly Sweeney: production book (Box Box 69)
  - A Month in the Country: sch., performance reports, research and background (Box Box 70)
  - A Month in the Country: sch. and performance reports (Box Box 70)
  - A Month in the Country: prompt book (Box Box 70)
  - Mrs. Klein: stage blue prints (Box Box 71)
  - Mrs. Klein: production book (Box Box 71)
  - Mrs. Klein: script, costume design and misc. items (Box Box 71)
  - My Children! My Africa!: script and audio tapes (Box Box 72)
  - My Children! My Africa!: script and sch. (Box Box 72)
  - Oak and Ivy: contact sheets (Box Box 73)
  - Oak and Ivy: show reports (Box Box 73)
  - Oak and Ivy: deck crew (Box Box 73)
  - Oak and Ivy: blocking sheets (Box Box 73)
  - Oak and Ivy: blocking sheets (Box Box 73)
  - Oak and Ivy: cost and Run (Box Box 73)
  - Oak and Ivy: sound (Box Box 73)
  - Oak and Ivy: props (Box Box 73)
  - Oak and Ivy: production book (Box Box 73)
  - Oak and Ivy: theater review (Box Box 73)
  - Oak and Ivy: accident report (Box Box 73)
  - Oak and Ivy: revised script (Box Box 74)
  - Oak and Ivy: research (Box Box 74)
  - Oak and Ivy: sch. (Box Box 74)
  - Oak and Ivy: notes (Box Box 74)
  - The Odyssey: tech notes, prop and costume lists (Box Box 75)
  - The Odyssey: call board notes (Box Box 75)
  - The Odyssey: calling script (Box Box 75)
  - The Odyssey: calling script (Box Box 75)
  - The Odyssey: blocking script (Box Box 75)
  - The Odyssey: blocking script (Box Box 75)
  - Of The I Sing: blocking script (Box Box 76)
  - Of Thee I sing: blocking script (Box Box 76)
  - Of Thee I Sing: calling script (Box Box 76)
  - Of Thee I Sing: calling script (Box Box 76)
  - Of Thee I Sing: vocal score (Box Box 77)
  - Of Thee I Sing: PR notes and call board info (Box Box 77)
  - Of Thee I Sing: costume and pre-set lists (Box Box 77)
  - Of Thee I Sing: piano I music, act I (Box Box 77)
  - Of Thee I Sing: Piano 2 music, Act I (Box Box 77)
  - Of Thee I Sing: Piano I music, Act II (Box Box 77)
  - Of Thee I Sing: Piano 2 music, Act II (Box Box 77)
  - Our Town: script with blocking notes, 1 of 3 (Box Box 78)
  - Our Town: script with blocking notes, 2 of 3 (Box Box 78)
  - Our Town: script with blocking notes, 3 of 3 (Box Box 78)
  - Our Town: back ground info, calendars and misc. lists (Box Box 79)
  - Our Town: program and script (Box Box 79)
  - Our Town: lighting info and stage managers packet (Box Box 79)
  - Playquest: production book, 1 of 2 (Box Box 80)
  - Playquest: production book, 2 of 2 (Box Box 80)
  - Playquest: production book/scripts, 1 of 3 (Box Box 80)
  - Playquest: production book/scripts, 2 of 3 (Box Box 80)
  - Playquest: production book/scripts, 3 of 3 (Box Box 80)
  - The Plough and the Stars: script with blocking notes (Box Box 81)
  - The Plough and the Stars:study guide/calendars and misc. production notes (Box Box 81)
  - The Price: prompt book (Box Box 82)
  - A Perfect Ganesh: script with blocking notes, 1 of 2 (Box Box 83)
  - A Prefect Ganesh: script with blocking notes, 2 of 2 (Box Box 83)
  - A Prefect Ganesh: SM notes, 1 of 2 (Box Box 83)
  - A Prefect Ganesh: SM notes, 2 of 2 (Box Box 83)
  - A Prefect Ganesh: production book with notes (Box Box 83)
  - Pygmalion: stage/prop setup, misc. production notes (Box Box 84)
  - Pygmalion: background info. /script with blocking notes (Box Box 84)
  - Pygmalion: script with blocking and notes (Box Box 84)
  - Pygmalion: script with blocking notes (Box Box 84)
  - The Revengers Comedies: schs., tech notes, cast info (Box Box 85)
  - The Revengers Comedies: blocking notes, set and prop info (Box Box 85)
  - The Revengers Comedies: schs., and performance reports (Box Box 85)
  - The Revengers Comedies: calling script, 1 of 3 (Box Box 86)
  - The Revengers Comedies: calling script, 2 of 3 (Box Box 86)
  - The revengers Comedies: calling script, 3 of 3 (Box Box 86)
  - The Revengers Comedies: blocking script (Box Box 86)
  - The Revengers Comedies: blocking script (Box Box 86)
  - A Room of Ones Own: misc. production info (Box Box 87)
  - Room Service: call script (Box Box 87)
  - The Royal Family: cast list (Box Box 88)
  - The Royal Family: rehearsal sch. (Box Box 88)
  - The Royal Family: rehearsal notes (Box Box 88)
  - The Royal Family: performance report (Box Box 88)
  - The Royal Family: cue master and sound cues sheets (Box Box 88)
  - The Royal Family: costume running (Box Box 88)
  - The Royal Family: the acting edition script, Act I (Box Box 88)
  - The Royal Family: acting edition script, Act II (Box Box 88)
  - The Royal Family: acting edition script, Act III (Box Box 88)
  - The Royal family: suggested text changes (Box Box 88)
  - The Royal Family: stage blue print (Box Box 88)
  - The Royal Family: prop. info and set pictures (Box Box 88)
  - The Royal Family: costumes (Box Box 88)
  - The Royal Family: furniture and decorations (Box Box 88)
  - The Royal Family: theater review (Box Box 88)
  - The School for Wives: misc. production materials (Box Box 89)
  - The School for Wives: blocking script (Box Box 89)
  - The Seagull: misc. production info (Box Box 90)
  - The Seagull: script (Box Box 90)
  - The Seagull: misc. production material (Box Box 90)
  - She Stoops to Conquer: script with notes (Box Box 91)
  - She Stoops to Conquer: misc. production material (Box Box 91)
  - Sin: production book and performance reports (Box Box 92)
  - Sin: production book and performance reports (Box Box 92)
  - Sin: misc. production materials (Box Box 92)
  - Sin: script revision (Box Box 92)
  - Skin of our Teeth: prompt script (Box Box 93)
  - Skin of our Teeth: script (Box Box 93)
  - Skin of our Teeth: script with notes (Box Box 93)
  - The Skin of our Teeth: script with notes (Box Box 94)